Pedro Moreira



pedrohenryque.rm@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/pedroh-moreira



+353 830038393



https://react-my-portfolio.vercel.app

Summary

As a web developer holding a Higher Certificate Diploma (NFQ level 6) at CCT College and immersed in studying Front-End development for more than 3 years, I have specialised in React. Building my latest projects have honed my aptitude with responsive layouts, user interfaces, wireframes, APIs, and frameworks, among other areas and technologies.

Experience

> Devops Agent

Accenture

Oct 2021 - Present (3 months +)

As an agent of the Developer Operations Team, I'm responsible for testing the compliance of apps that are using the client provided integrations such as Login, Sign Up, Share, Likes, and many others.

The routine consists of testing apps and web applications and then reporting bugs and not compliant features to the developers, also escalating suspicious behaviours;

Content Moderator

Accenture

Oct 2020 - Oct 2021 (1 year 1 month)

As a Content Moderator, I'm responsible for analysing and reviewing the content escalating and/or resolving issues that are reported by users or flagged by the system;

Achievements: I was awarded by my company for developing web applications with Javascript, CSS, HTML and AppScript that improved the agents routing, resulting in an increase of productivity and also provided better data collection and analysis.

Senior Administrative Assistant

Faurgs- TI

Apr 2014 - Mar 2017 (3 years)

Education

cct CCT College Dublin

Higher Diploma (NFQ Level 6), Web Development Nov 2020 - Jan 2021



Online Bootcamp, Web Development

Licenses & Certifications

Source Control - Udacity

https://www.udacity.com/course/version-control-with-git--ud123

- in Learning Full-Stack JavaScript Development: MongoDB, Node, and React LinkedIn
- Foundations: Data Analysis Google coursera.org/verify/KB3D5WVZ5DHX

Skills

JavaScript • Full-Stack Development • Web Development • React.js • TypeScript • Node.js • Web Services API • Version Control • Front-End Development • SASS

Honors & Awards

> Received recognition - Accenture

May 2021

Recognition Points awarded for the creation of Web Applications after its implementation across projects;